bpovia.com 2015-04-20

# Privacy Policy - BPOVIA Virtual Assistant and Knowledge Process Outsourcing Service

BPOVIA Ltd. takes the privacy of your personal information very seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. In order to operate BPOVIA's services and to reduce the risk of fraud, BPOVIA Ltd., ("BPOVIA" or "we") must ask you to provide us information about yourself and your credit card and/or bank account when applying for one of BPOVIA™'s services. BPOVIA uses your information to process applications, complete transactions, respond to your requests, deliver the services in which you enroll or for which you apply, and notify you of special offers that we think may interest you. We also use your information to provide you with a more effective customer experience while interacting with our agents or our website. 

We WILL NOT sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies to all services that are provided by BPOVIA Ltd. 

By accepting the Privacy Policy and Terms of Service in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the BPOVIA Terms of Service. This Privacy Policy will take effect on January 1, 2008.

 **Information We Collect**  
To open an account with BPOVIA, you must provide your name, address, phone number, valid e-mail address. In order to make payments or purchases on your behalf, you may be required to provide credit card, debit card or bank account information. This required information is necessary for us to process transactions, protect you against credit card fraud and checking account fraud, and to contact you should the need arise in administering your account. 

**How the Information is Used**  
We collect, store and process your information in order to 1) provide our services and process your transactions, to 2) provide customer service, to 3) determine your eligibility to receive offers for special features or products and to 4) improve our products and services.   
We disclose information that we in, good faith, believe is appropriate to cooperate in investigations of fraud or other illegal activity, or to conduct investigations of violations of our Terms of Service. We disclose information in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, levy, attachment, order of a court-appointed receiver or other comparable legal process, including subpoenas from private parties in a civil action.

 **Information Security  
** BPOVIA is committed to handling customer information with the highest industry standards for information security. Credit card, bank account and other personal information are stored only in encrypted form. We restrict access to your personally identifiable information to employees who need to know that information in order to provide services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard nonpublic personal information. 

**Customer Service Correspondence**  
If you send us correspondence via e-mail, instant messenger, or facsimile, we retain such information in the records of your account. All correspondence with BPOVIA agents via telephone is recorded and stored in the records of your account. We will also retain customer service correspondence and other correspondence from BPOVIA to you for a period of six months. We retain these records in order to measure and improve our customer service, and to investigate potential fraud and violations of our Terms of Service. We may, over time, delete these records if permitted by law. 

**Our Contact with BPOVIA Customers**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis via e-mail, telephone and instant messenger to provide requested services, and we also communicate via these media to resolve customer complaints. We use your e-mail address to confirm your opening of an account with BPOVIA, to send information about important changes to our products and services, and to send notices and other disclosures required by law. Generally, users cannot opt out of these communications, but they will be primarily informational in nature rather than promotional. 

**Changes to This Policy  
** We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as our Services change and expand. If we are going to use or disclose your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time we collected the information, you will have a choice as to whether or not we use or disclose your information in this new manner. Any material changes will be effective only after we provide you by e-mail with at least 30 days' notice of the amended Privacy Policy (if you have closed your account with BPOVIA, you will not be contacted to notify you of the amended Policy and your personal information will not be used or disclosed in this new manner).

 **This Site Contains Links to Other Sites**  
BPOVIA Ltd. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other websites to which the Site links or to which link to the Site. By clicking on a link, logo or other item, please note that you may no longer be on the BPOVIA Site. To check what Internet location you are on, note the URL at the top and/or bottom of your browser. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement of that website whenever interacting with any website. 

**Questions and Suggestions**  
If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at: [contact@bpovia.com](mailto:contact@bpovia.com)
